{
    "subject": "resource/Dry_well",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Nuclear_power_plant_components",
    "human_readable": "The dry well is about Nuclear power plant components.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6069818139076233,
            "question": "What types of components are found in a nuclear power plant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.546432614326477,
            "question": "What materials are commonly used in constructing components of a nuclear power plant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33040329813957214,
            "question": "How does nuclear fission generate energy in a power plant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2742178738117218,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges associated with waste disposal from nuclear power plants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26075229048728943,
            "question": "What is the function of a turbine in a nuclear power plant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2574158310890198,
            "question": "Can you describe the purpose of a reactor vessel in a nuclear power plant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2140781134366989,
            "question": "What safety features are essential for preventing accidents in a nuclear power plant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20354385673999786,
            "question": "How does a steam generator contribute to electricity production in a nuclear power plant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11536373198032379,
            "question": "Describe the process of cooling a nuclear reactor."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07115701586008072,
            "question": "What role do control rods play in a nuclear reactor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The dry well is about Nuclear power plant components.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2909_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Describe the process of cooling a nuclear reactor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2909_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does a steam generator contribute to electricity production in a nuclear power plant?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2909_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What safety features are essential for preventing accidents in a nuclear power plant?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2909_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2909_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2909_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2909_151.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2909_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2909_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2909_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2909_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2909_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2909_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2909_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more queries! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly describes various components of a nuclear power plant, including the dry well. Therefore, it supports the statement that \"The dry well is about Nuclear power plant components.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}